So now that we have defined what neural networks are,
ニューラルネットワークとは何かを定義したので
we need to learn how to train them.
そのトレーニング方法を学ぶ必要があります
Training them really means what parameters should they
トレーニングとは実際には
have on the edges in order to model our data well.
データをモデル化するためにエッジに必要なパラメーターを意味します
So in order to learn how to train them,
トレーニング方法を学ぶためには
we need to look carefully at how they process the input to obtain an output.
出力を求めるために入力をどのように処理するかをよく見る必要があります
So let's look at our simplest neural network, a perceptron.
では単純なニューラルネットワークであるパーセプトロンを見てみましょう
This perceptron receives a data point of the form x1,
このパーセプトロンはx1 x2という形式のデータポイントを
x2 where the label is Y=1.
受け取り ラベルはY=1です
This means that the point is blue.
これはポイントが青であることを意味します
Now the perceptron is defined by a linear equation say w1, x1 plus w2,
パーセプトロンは線形式によって定義され たとえば w1 x1プラスｗ2
x2 plus B, where w1 and w2 are the weights in the edges and B is the bias in the note.
x2プラスBです  w1とw2はエッジの 重みであり Bはノートのバイアスです
Here, w1 is bigger than w2,
ここでは w1はw2より大きいので
so we'll denote that by drawing the edge labelled w1
w1というラベルのエッジをw2というラベルのエッジより
much thicker than the edge labelled w2.
太く描いて そのことを示します
Now, what the perceptron does is it plots the point x1,
では パーセプトロンがすることは ポイントx1 x2をプロットし
x2 and it outputs the probability that the point is blue.
ポイントが青である確率を出力することです
Here is the point is in the red area and then the output is a small number,
ここではポイントは赤のエリアにあり 出力は小さな数です
since the point is not very likely to be blue.
ポイントが青である可能性は非常に低いからです
This process is known as feedforward.
このプロセスをフィードフォワードといいます
We can see that this is a bad model because the point is actually blue.
これは良くないモデルであることがわかります ポイントは実際には青だからです
Given that the third coordinate,
第3の座標として
the Y is one.
Yが1であるとします
Now if we have a more complicated neural network,
より複雑なニューラルネットワークの場合も
then the process is the same.
プロセスは同じです
Here, we have thick edges corresponding to large weights and
ここに 大きな重みに対応する太いエッジと
thin edges corresponding to small weights and the neural network plots
小さな重みに対応する細いエッジがあり ニューラルネットワークは
the point in the top graph and also in
上のグラフと
the bottom graph and the outputs coming out will be a small number from the top model.
下のグラフにポイントをプロットし 結果としての出力は上のモデルから小さな数になります
The point lies in the red area which means it has a small probability of being
ポイントが赤のエリアにあるということは 青である確率が低いことを意味し
blue and a large number from the second model,
2番目のモデルからの大きな数は
since the point lies in the blue area which means
ポイントが青のエリアにあるために
it has a large probability of being blue.
青である確率が高いこと意味します
Now, as the two models get combined into this nonlinear model and
2つのモデルが組み合わされて この非線形モデルになり
the output layer just plots
出力層は
the point and it tells the probability that the point is blue.
ポイントをプロットして ポイントが青である確率を示します
As you can see, this is a bad model because it
見てのとおり これは良くないモデルです
puts the point in the red area and the point is blue.
ポイントを赤のエリアに置いていますが ポイントは青だからです
Again, this process called feedforward and we'll look at it more carefully.
このプロセスはフィードフォワードと呼ばれます もう少し詳しく見てみましょう
Here, we have our neural network and the other notations so the bias is in the outside.
これは同じニューラルネットワークの別の表記であり バイアスが外側にあります
Now we have a matrix of weights.
重みの行列があります
The matrix w superscript one denoting the first layer and the entries are the weights w1,
行列wの上付き文字1は最初の層を示し エントリーは重みw11
1 up to w3, 2.
からw32までです
Notice that the biases have now been written as w3,
バイアスがw31とw32として書かれていますが
1 and w3, 2 this is just for convenience.
これは利便性のためにすぎません
Now in the next layer,
次の層にも
we also have a matrix this one is w superscript two for the second layer.
行列があり wの上付き文字2は2番目の層であることを示します
This layer contains the weights that tell us how to combine
この層が含んでいる重みから 最初の層の
the linear models in the first layer to obtain the nonlinear model in the second layer.
線形モデルを組み合わせて 2番目の層の非線形モデルを得る方法がわかります
Now what happens is some math.
次に起こるのは ちょっとした計算です
We have the input in the form x1, x2,
入力はx1 x2 1という形式であり
1 where the one comes from the bias unit.
1はバイアスユニットから来ています
Now we multiply it by the matrix w1 to get these outputs.
これに行列w1をかけて これらの出力を求めます
Then, we apply the sigmoid function to turn the outputs into values between zero and one.
次に シグモイド関数を適用して 出力を0と1の間の値に変換します
Then the vector format these values gets a one attatched for
次にベクターフォーマットでこれらの値にバイアスユニットの1を
the bias unit and multiplied by the second matrix.
（バイアス単位に）付加された値と二番目の行列とかけます
This returns an output that now gets thrown into a sigmoid function to
これから返される出力をシグモイド関数にスローして
obtain the final output which is y-hat.
最終的な出力である yハットが得られます
Y-hat is the prediction or the probability that the point is labeled blue.
yハットはポイントが青のラベルを付けられる予測値または確率です
So this is what neural networks do.
これが ニューラルネットワークがすることです
They take the input vector and then apply
入力ベクターを取り
a sequence of linear models and sigmoid functions.
線形モデルとシグモイド関数のシーケンスを適用します
These maps when combined become a highly non-linear map.
これらのマップを組み合わせると非常な非線形マップになります
And the final formula is simply y-hat equals sigmoid of
また 最終的な式は単純なyハット イコール
w2 combined with sigmoid of w1 applied to x.
w2のシグモイド結合w1のシグモイドをxに適用となります
Just for redundance, we do this again on a multi-layer perceptron or neural network.
冗長性のために これを多層パーセプトロンまたはニューラルネットワークで再び行います
To calculate our prediction y-hat,
予測値yハットを計算するには
we start with the unit vector x,
ユニットベクターxから始めて
then we apply the first matrix and
最初の行列と
a sigmoid function to get the values in the second layer.
シグモイド関数を適用して2番目の層の値を得ます
Then, we apply the second matrix and another sigmoid function to get the values on
次に2番目の行列ともうひとつのシグモイド関数を適用して
the third layer and so on and so forth until we get our final prediction, y-hat.
3番目の層の値を求め 最終的な予測値yハットが得られるまで続けます
And this is the feedforward process that the neural networks
また これはニューラルネットワークが入力ベクターから
use to obtain the prediction from the input vector.
予測値を求めるために使用するフィードフォワードプロセスです